<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Brussels Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="category_landmarks">Landmarks</string>
    <string name="category_events">Events</string>
    <string name="category_restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="category_bars">Bars</string>
    <string name="category_hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="location_details">Location details</string>
    <!-- Landmarks Fragment Resource (@Wikipedia.org)  -->
    <!-- Resources for the Grand Place -->
    <string name="grand_place">Grand Place</string>
    <string name="grand_place_address">Grand Place, B-1000</string>
    <string name="grand_place_description">The Grand Place in French or Grote Markt in Dutch,
        is the central square of Brussels. It is surrounded by opulent guildhalls and two larger
        edifices, the city\'s Town Hall, and the Breadhouse (French: Maison du Roi, Dutch: Broodhuis)
        building containing the Museum of the City of Brussels. The square is the most important
        tourist destination and most memorable landmark in Brussels. It measures 68 by 110 metres
        (223 by 361 ft), and it is a UNESCO World Heritage Site.</string>
    <!-- Resources for the Manneken Pis -->
    <string name="manneken_pis">Manneken Pis</string>
    <string name="manneken_pis_address">Corner of Rue du Chene and Rue de l\'Etuve, B-1000 Brussels</string>
    <string name="manneken_pis_description">Manneken Pis, meaning "Little man Pee" in Dutch) is a
        landmark small bronze sculpture (61 cm) in Brussels, depicting a naked little boy
        urinating into a fountain\'s basin. It was designed by Hiëronymus Duquesnoy the Elder and put
        in place in 1618 or 1619. To find it, one takes the left lane next to the Brussels Town Hall
        from the famous Grand Place and walks a few hundred metres southwest via Rue Charles
        Buls/Karel Bulsstraat.</string>
    <!-- Resources for the Atomium -->
    <string name="atomium">Atomium</string>
    <string name="atomium_address">Square de l\'Atomium, B-1020 Brussels</string>
    <string name="atomium_description">The Atomium is a building in Brussels originally constructed
        for Expo 58, the 1958 Brussels World\'s Fair. Designed by the engineer André Waterkeyn and
        architects André and Jean Polak, it stands 102 m (335 ft) tall. Its nine 18 m (60 ft)
        diameter stainless steel clad spheres are connected so that the whole forms the shape of a
        unit cell of an iron crystal magnified 165 billion times. It is now a museum.</string>
    <!-- Resources for the Mini-Europe -->
    <string name="mini_europe">Mini-Europe</string>
    <string name="mini_europe_address">Bruparck, B-1020 Brussels</string>
    <string name="mini_europe_description">Mini-Europe is a miniature park located in Bruparck at
        the foot of the Atomium in Brussels, Belgium. Mini-Europe has reproductions of monuments in
        the European Union on show, at a scale of 1:25. Roughly 80 cities and 350 buildings are
        represented. Mini-Europe receives 350,000 visitors per year and has a turnover of 4 million
        Euros. The park contains live action models such as trains, mills, an erupting Mount Vesuvius,
        and cable cars. A guide gives the details on all the monuments. At the end of the visit, the
        “Spirit of Europe” exhibition gives an interactive overview of the European Union in the form
        of multimedia games. The park is built on an area of 24,000 m². The initial investment was
        of €10 million in 1989, on its inauguration by Prince Philip of Belgium.</string>
    <!-- Resources for the Parc du Cinquantenaire -->
    <string name="parc_cinquantenaire">Parc du Cinquantenaire</string>
    <string name="parc_cinquantenaire_address">Parc du Cinquantenaire, B-1000 Brussels</string>
    <string name="parc_cinquantenaire_description">Parc du Cinquantenaire (French for "Park of the
        Fiftieth Anniversary", or Jubelpark (Dutch for "Jubilee Park") is a large public, urban park
        (30 hectares) in the easternmost part of the European Quarter in Brussels, Belgium. Most buildings
        of the U-shaped complex which dominate the park were commissioned by the Belgian government
        under the patronage of King Leopold II for the 1880 National Exhibition commemorating the
        fiftieth anniversary of Belgian independence. During successive exhibitions in the same area,
        more structures were added. The centrepiece triumphal arch was erected in 1905 replacing a
        previous temporary version of the arcade by Gédéon Bordiau. The structures were built in iron,
        glass and stone, symbolising the economic and industrial performance of Belgium. The surrounding
        30-hectare park esplanade was full of picturesque gardens, ponds and waterfalls. It housed
        several trade fairs, exhibitions and festivals at the beginning of the century. In 1930 the
        government decided to reserve Cinquantenaire for use as a leisure park.\n\nThe Royal Military Museum
        has been the sole tenant of the northern half of the complex since 1880. The southern half
        is occupied by the Jubelpark museum (Cinquantenaire Museum) and the AutoWorld Museum. The
        Temple of Human Passions, a remainder from 1886, and the Great Mosque of Brussels from 1978
        are located in the north-western corner of the park.\n\nLine 1 of the Brussels Metro
        and the Belliard Tunnel from wetstraat pass underneath the park, the latter partly in an open
        section in front of the Arch. The nearest metro stations are Schuman to the west of the park,
        and Mérode immediately to the east.</string>
    <!-- Resources for the Musical Instrument Museum -->
    <string name="musical_instrument_museum">Musical Instrument Museum</string>
    <string name="musical_instrument_museum_address">Rue Montagne de la Cour 2, B-1000 Brussels</string>
    <string name="musical_instrument_museum_description">The Musical Instruments Museum (MIM) is a
        music museum in central Brussels, Belgium. It is part of the Royal Museums for Art and
        History and internationally renowned for its collection of over 8,000 instruments.\n\nThe
        museum\'s collection represents Belgian musical history (including Brussels\' importance in
        the making of recorders in the 18th and 19th centuries and as the home of instrument inventor
        Adolphe Sax in the 19th century), European musical traditions, and non-European instruments.
        Mechanical instruments are shown in the basement, traditional instruments on the ground floor,
        the development of the modern orchestral instruments on the first floor, and keyboard and
        stringed instruments on the second floor.\n\nAmong the notable pieces of the collection are
        the famous Rottenburgh Alto recorder, instruments invented by Adolphe Sax, a unique set of
        giant Chinese stone chimes, and the only existing copy of the luthéal, an instrument used
        by Ravel.</string>
    <!-- Resources for the Cathedral of St. Michael and St. Gudula -->
    <string name="cathedral_michael_gudula">Cathedral of St. Michael and St. Gudula</string>
    <string name="cathedral_michael_gudula_address">Place Sainte-Gudule, B-1000 Brussels</string>
    <string name="cathedral_michael_gudula_description">The Cathedral of St. Michael and St. Gudula
        (French: Co-Cathédrale collégiale des Ss-Michel et Gudule, Dutch: Collegiale Sint-Michiels-
        en Sint-Goedele-co-kathedraal) is a Roman Catholic church in Brussels, Belgium. The church
        was given cathedral status in 1962 and has since been the co-cathedral of the Archdiocese
        of Mechelen-Brussels, together with St. Rumbold\'s Cathedral in Mechelen.\n\nA chapel dedicated
        to St. Michael was probably built on the Treurenberg hill as early as the 9th century. In the
        11th century it was replaced by a Romanesque church. In 1047, Lambert II, Count of Leuven
        founded a chapter in this church and organized the transportation of the relics of the martyr
        St. Gudula, housed before then in Saint Gaugericus Church on Saint-Géry Island. The patron
        saints of the church, St. Michael and St. Gudula, are also the patron saints of the city of
        Brussels.\n\nIn the thirteenth century, Henry I, Duke of Brabant ordered two round towers to
        be added to the church. Henry II, Duke of Brabant instructed the building of a Gothic collegiate
        church in 1226. The choir was constructed between 1226 and 1276. It took about 300 years to
        complete the entire church. It was completed just before the reign of the emperor Charles V
        commenced in 1519.</string>
    <!-- Resources for the Belgian Comic Strip Center -->
    <string name="belgian_comic_strip_center">Belgian Comic Strip Center</string>
    <string name="belgian_comic_strip_center_address">Rue des Sables/Zandstraat 20, B-1000 Brussels</string>
    <string name="belgian_comic_strip_center_description">The Belgian Comic Strip Center (French: Centre
        belge de la Bande dessinée, Dutch: Belgisch Stripcentrum) is a museum in Brussels, dedicated
        to Belgian comics.\n\nOn the ground floor of the museum a restaurant can be found, a room
        dedicated to Victor Horta, a comics\' store named "Slumberland" after Little Nemo in Slumberland,
        a library with a reading room and study center. The first floor has an auditorium, a room with
        original comic book pages by various artists and a room dedicated to animation, more specifically
        the Belgian animation industry, such as Belvision.\n\nThe second floor has a permanent exhibition
        dedicated to the chronological history of the medium in Belgium called "The Museum of Imagination".
        The exhibit starts off with Hergé and ends with Peyo, covering the pioneers of Belgian comics
        between 1929 and 1958 and with special focus on the magazines Spirou and Tintin. Each artist
        has a room dedicated to his work and designed in a playful way.\n\nThe final floor is dedicated
        to the merchandising of comics and available for provisional exhibitions.</string>
    <!-- Resources for the Royal Greenhouses of Laeken -->
    <string name="royal_greenhouses_laeken">Royal Greenhouses of Laeken</string>
    <string name="royal_greenhouses_laeken_address">Avenue du Parc Royal, B-1020 Brussels</string>
    <string name="royal_greenhouses_laeken_description">The Royal Greenhouses of Laeken (Dutch: Koninklijke
        Serres van Laken, French: Serres Royales de Laeken) are a vast complex of monumental heated
        greenhouses in the park of the Royal Castle of Laeken in the north of Brussels. The greenhouses
        are world famous, but not a tourist attraction. The greenhouses are part of the Royal Park,
        and the royal private gardens and usually not open for visitors.\n\nThe gardens date of the
        18th century, but King Leopold II changed the its garden-architecture. A brand new complex
        was commissioned by King Leopold II and designed by Alphonse Balat. Built between 1874 and
        1895, the complex was finished with the completion of the so-called "Iron Church", a domed
        greenhouse that would originally serve as the royal chapel. The total floor surface of this
        immense complex is 2.5 hectares (270,000 square feet). 800,000 liters (over 200,000 US gallons)
        of fuel oil are needed each year to heat the buildings. After the death of the king the
        greenhouses were kept, but the Iron church was conversed into a private royal bathing house.
        \n\nFamous is the royal botanic collection, with old plants from Africa and various species
        of flowers that are cultivated inside the royal greenhouses for use at court.\n\nThe royal
        complex can only be visited during a two-week period in April–May each year, when most flowers
        are in full bloom.</string>
    <!-- Resources for the Royal Palace of Brussels -->
    <string name="royal_palace_brussels">Royal Palace of Brussels</string>
    <string name="royal_palace_brussels_address"> Rue Brederode 16, B-1020 Brussels</string>
    <string name="royal_palace_brussels_description">The Royal Palace of Brussels (Dutch: Koninklijk
        Paleis van Brussel, French: Palais Royal de Bruxelles, German: Königlicher Palast von Brüssel)
        is the official palace of the King and Queen of the Belgians in the centre of the nation\'s
        capital Brussels. However it is not used as a royal residence, as the king and his family live
        in the Royal Palace of Laeken on the outskirts of Brussels.\n\nThe palace is situated in
        front of Brussels Park. A long square called the Paleizenplein/Place des Palais separates the
        palace from the park. The middle axis of the park marks both the middle peristyle of the
        palace and the middle of the facing building on the other side of the park, which is the
        Palace of the Nation (the Belgian Federal Parliament building). The two facing buildings are
        said to symbolize Belgium\'s system of government: a constitutional monarchy.</string>
    <!-- Events Fragment Resource (@www.brussels.be) -->
    <!-- Resources for the BXL Tour -->
    <string name="bxl_tour">BXL Tour</string>
    <string name="bxl_tour_address">Carrefour des Attelages in the Bois de la Cambre, B-1050 Brussels</string>
    <string name="bxl_tour_description">On Sunday 25 June 2017, from 9 am, with start and finish at
        the Bois de la Cambre.\n\nBXL Tour is a 50-km bike ride through the streets of the capital.
        The tour goes along various places of the city such as the Bois de la Cambre, Cinquantenaire,
        Atomium, King Baudouin Stadium and the Avenues Louise and Tervuren. The Carrefour des Attelages
        at the Bois de la Cambre is transformed into Velocity, a place of discoveries with many
        activities for young and old: alternative tours, initiations, demonstrations,etc.\n\nAnd all of
        this with music and food stands.</string>
    <!-- Resources for the Ommegang 2017 -->
    <string name="ommegang_2017">Ommegang 2017</string>
    <string name="ommegang_2017_address">Grand Place, B-1000</string>
    <string name="ommegang_2017_description">In Brussels, from 5 to 7 July 2017.\n\nOn 5 and 7 July,
        on the Grand-Place, from 8:45 pm, a historic parade, part of the Brussels folklore with more
        than 1.400 actors, folk and historic groups, horses, puppet theater, giants, flags,etc. It
        honours the coming of Charles the Fifth to Brussels in 1549.\n\nIn the Brussels Park (Parc
        de Bruxelles - Warandepark) there will be a free medieval village with tournaments on 5, 6,
        7 and 8 July (from noon to 9 pm). At the Place Agora and behind the Stock Exchange there will
        be a medieval market (from noon to 9 pm).\n\nSince 2012 the Ommegang is also part of the
        Carolus V Festival, a festival celebrating Emperor Charles V and his Palace of the Coudenberg.</string>
    <!-- Resources for the Brussels Beach 2017 -->
    <string name="brussels_beach_2017">Brussels Beach 2017</string>
    <string name="brussels_beach_2017_address">Quai des Péniches, B-1000</string>
    <string name="brussels_beach_2017_description">Brussels Beach (Bruxelles les Bains) opens its
        urban beach from 7 July to 13 August 2017, from Tuesday till Sunday, at the Quai des Péniches
        near the Place Sainctelette.\n\nThere will be lots of events and activities for young and old.
        Parties with the best DJ\'s of the capital start at the Croisetteke and go on on the Boat Club
        during a cruise on the Canal of Brussels.</string>
    <!-- Resources for the Brussels Summer Festival 2017 -->
    <string name="brussels_summer_festival_2017">Brussels Summer Festival 2017</string>
    <string name="brussels_summer_festival_2017_address">Place des Palais, B-1000</string>
    <string name="brussels_summer_festival_2017_description">From 6 to 15 August 2017 on and around the
        Place des Palais.\n\n16th edition of the BSF with concerts and cultural events at the Place
        des Palais and Mont des Arts.\n\nSchedule: Pet Shop Boys, Puggy, Black Box Revelation, Feist,
        Goose, Milow, Orbital, Boulevard des Airs, Henri PFR, Jain, La Femme, MHD, Trust, Noa, Alex
        Germys, Teemid, Krono, Rinôçérôse, Typh Barrow, Magyd Cherfi, Pierce Brothers, Faon Faon,
        Oyster Node, Viktor Lazlo, Konoba, Lisa Leblanc and Ivan Paduart (+ Quentin Dujardin and Manu
        Katché), etc.</string>
    <!-- Resources for the Flowertime -->
    <string name="flowertime">Flowertime</string>
    <string name="flowertime_address">Grand Place, B-1000</string>
    <string name="flowertime_description">FFrom 11 to 15 August 2017 at the City Hall of Brussels
        and the Grand Place.\n\nThe City of Brussels and the association of the Brussels Flower
        Carpet join forces for Flowertime, an international plant and flower arrangement event. The
        event takes place biannually, alternating with the Flower Carpet.\n\nFlowertime transforms
        the City Hall and Grand Place into a floral dream. And this year\'s theme should put you in
        the best of moods right away: flowers and fruits. For five days, you will be able to stroll
        through dozens of colorful and fruity creations from Belgian top florists.</string>
    <!-- Resources for the Nuit Blanche 2017 -->
    <string name="nuit_blanche_2017">Nuit Blanche 2017</string>
    <string name="nuit_blanche_2017_address">Quartier des Libertés, B-1000</string>
    <string name="nuit_blanche_2017_description">In the night from Saturday 7 to Sunday 8 October
        2017 at the Parc de Bruxelles (Royal Park) and the Quartier des Libertés (formerly Notre-Dame-aux-Neiges.)
        \n\nNuit Blanche is a night (7 pm - 3 am) where people can come together, a night where unusual
        and contemporary creativity come together in a pleasant and festive atmosphere. Program:
        installations, performances, multimedia projections, concerts, interactive events, performances
        by DJs and VJs, etc.\n\nThe theme of the 2017 edition is \'Power Games\'.</string>
    <!-- Restaurants Fragment Resource -->
    <!-- Resources for Le Chou de Bruxelles -->
    <string name="chou_brussels">Le Chou de Bruxelles</string>
    <string name="chou_brussels_address">Rue de florence 26, B-1050 Brussels</string>
    <string name="chou_brussels_description">Our restaurant "Le Chou de Bruxelles" is happy to receive
        you in one of the most beautifull area of Ixelles, located between the Avenue Louise and the
        famous Châtelain.\n\nIn a Belgo-Belgian setting local cooking is served to you.\n\nOur
        speciality: MUSSELS, prepared in 30 different way, made our reputation since 20 years now.
        \n\nNonesuch in Brussels, compose your self your "Menu Carte" (starter-maincourse-dessert) for 30€.
        \n\nWhen the weather is nice, a wonderful garden will welcome you, we can cover it when it
        rains.</string>
    <!-- Resources for Le Grand Café -->
    <string name="grand_cafe">Le Grand café</string>
    <string name="grand_cafe_address">Boulevard Anspach 78, B-1000 Brussels</string>
    <string name="grand_cafe_description">Dining options: After-hours, Drinks, Dinner, Breakfast,
        Brunch, Lunch, Accepts American Express, Accepts Discover, Accepts Mastercard, Accepts Visa,
        Digital Payments, Free Wifi, Full Bar, Highchairs Available, Outdoor Seating, Reservations,
        Seating, Serves Alcohol, Takeout, Television, Waitstaff, Wheelchair Accessible.</string>
    <!-- Resources for Le Pickwick -->
    <string name="pickwick">Le Pickwick</string>
    <string name="pickwick_address">Avenue Adolphe Buyl 79, B-1050 Brussels</string>
    <string name="pickwick_description">BELGIAN BREWER - Located in Brussels, discover this typical
        Belgian brewery: Pickwick, as welcoming as a gourmet restaurant, which is waiting for you!\n\n
        QUALITY OF MISE - The menu offers a good selection of typical Belgian brasserie dishes. The
        products are chosen with care and the kitchen is mastered, for quality plates and to make
        you happy!\n\nWITH FRIENDS - The welcome is warm and familiar, for the feeling to come and
        eat with friends in a friendly atmosphere and relaxation. Ideal for small groups, friends or
        family!</string>
    <!-- Resources for the WY Brussels -->
    <string name="wy_brussels">WY Brussels</string>
    <string name="wy_brussels_address">Rue Bodenbroek 22 to 24, B-1000 Brussels</string>
    <string name="wy_brussels_description">Michelin Guide\n\nA gastronomic haven in the heart of the
        \"Mercedes House\" in Brussels. Behind the cars on display, we find this bright, contemporary
        restaurant and its kitchen full of qualities: good products, creativity, refinement, etc,
        screens allow even see the chefs at work. The showroom spirit!</string>
    <!-- Resources for the Green Mango -->
    <string name="green_mango">Green Mango</string>
    <string name="green_mango_address">Chaussée de Vleurgat 142, B-1000 Brussels</string>
    <string name="green_mango_description">Warm colors, world music and all styles, generous food and
        original ingredients, fresh fruit cocktails, alcoholic or not. It\'s not a secret, we expect
        you to travel during your meal.\n\nHere, no fuss, we go straight to the point. People come to
        enjoy crazy Burgers, excellent Thai soups or salads of all kinds while sipping a smoothie with
        tropical flavors or a refreshing milkshake.\n\nEach of our Burgers was created, worked, and
        tested individually. Our card has been created by itself, and the products you find have all
        proved themselves.\n\nOur golden rules are: we constantly attach the greatest attention to
        quality and freshness of the products.</string>
    <!-- Bars Fragment Resource -->
    <!-- Resources for the Moeder Lambic (@wikipedia) -->
    <string name="moeder_lambic">Moeder Lambic</string>
    <string name="moeder_lambic_address">Place Fontainas 8, B-1000 Brussels</string>
    <string name="moeder_lambic_description">Moeder Lambic commonly refers to two different bars in
        the Brussels area owned by Jean Hummler, Nassim Dessicy, and Andy Mengal. The original
        location in the Saint-Gilles area of Brussels, called Chez Moeder Lambic, was established in
        the 1980s. In 2006, Jean and Nassim, who were bartenders at the time, purchased the business
        from the owners during bankruptcy. The success of the bar under Jean and Nassim led to the
        opening of a second location with third partner (Andy) near the center of Brussels at Place
        Fontainas. Today, both locations are known for their selection of lambic as well as non-lambic
        Belgian beers.\n\nBoth Moeder Lambic bars have a wide selection of lambic and other Belgian
        beers in draught and in bottle. The bars have also played host to Cantillon\'s Zwanze Day
        events. Though no specific lambics have been bottled for the bars, the draught list generally
        includes many beers from Cantillon, 3 Fonteinen, and other lambic brewers and blender that are
        not commonly found outside of the breweries or various festivals. However, there is one
        fruited lambic, Cantillon Cuvée Moeder, that is served exclusively at the bars.</string>
    <!-- Resources for La Porte Noire (@http://www.laportenoire.be) -->
    <string name="porte_noire">La Porte Noire</string>
    <string name="porte_noire_address">Rue des Alexiens 67, B-1000 Brussels</string>
    <string name="porte_noire_description">The Porte Noire traces its history back to the 16th
        century, with its subterranean vaulted ceilings, a water well and vintage icebox. In fact,
        this enchanting tavern once served as a kitchen for the nuns of the Alexien Convent.\n\nLong
        abandoned after the nuns\' departure, the cellar was finally restored in 1995 and converted
        into what has become one of Brussels\' most popular beer and whisky taverns. Its fine choice
        of beverages, knowledgeable barmen, and medieval atmosphere give the tavern a truly Celtic
        feel. No wonder the tavern\'s three central rooms have hosted so many memorable Saint
        Patrick\'s Day parties.\n\nOf course, just about any occasion is a good reason to celebrate
        at the Porte Noire and hardly a week goes by without live music, whisky tasting or a night
        of serious partying.\n\nSo push the door, walk down the stairs, and discover 100 exceptional
        Belgian beers, 11 taps, 80 fine brands of whisky, friendly barmen, rock and roots, and a
        decidedly relaxed ambience-all in an unforgettable Celtic setting!</string>
    <!-- Resources for Le Pantin (@www.lepantin.be) -->
    <string name="pantin">Le Pantin</string>
    <string name="pantin_address">Chaussée d\'Ixelles 355, B-1050 Brussels</string>
    <string name="pantin_description">Le Pantin is a cozy and friendly bar in which you can easily
        share your evening with many strangers. Its decor is a joyful brothel of bric à pic recovered,
        accumulated and assembled with care as its 30 years of existence, by Jean-Marie, my dad!
        \n\nSince 2011 it is also a second floor, a more intimate atmosphere in the hollow of an old
        armchair in the shade of a candle, where you can also share an evening with friends around
        a good game or Lose themselves in the pages of the many books hidden there. This part of the
        bar is also perfect for birthday parties or other festive meetings.\n\nWe keep the bar with
        the family, the dad who no longer serves beers but continues his tinkering and tinkering of
        all kinds, brother Tom who will not hesitate to offer a small Yagermeister to the most
        friendly of you, brother Kevin always Ready to support us and give a helping hand and I who
        prepare Breton cookies every lunch of the week and concocte you a small musical program every
        month!\n\nAnd do not forget the essential: a cheerful team of students to help us make you
        spend a good evening !!</string>
    <!-- Resources for the Delirium Café (@www.deliriumcafe.be) -->
    <string name="delirium_cafe">Delirium Café</string>
    <string name="delirium_cafe_address">Impasse de la Fidélité 4, B-1000 Brussels</string>
    <string name="delirium_cafe_description">No wonder Beer lovers from around the world love this
        place. You can taste more than 2000 beers from around the globe. Delirium Café holds the
        Guinness World Record for the most beers offered with 2004, obtained in 2004. Today we are
        getting close to 2500!\n\nYou will be able to choose from the famous Trappists, Belgian
        Abbeys, strong dark or lighter fruit beers from Belgium, beers from around the world ,
        unusual beers like Chocolate, Banana or Coco beers and more and more!!!\n\nCan\'t make up
        your mind? Don\'t worry. Our staff is here to help. And they will listen to you before
        proposing different choices! All tastes are admitted. Having said that, quality goes first.
        You will have to insist to drink more industrial products! But hey, customer is king!\n\nAdd
        to that a great decor, thousands of beer memorabilia items like old advertising plaques,
        trays, glasses, our jam sessions every Thursdays, concerts,etc. and get ready to enjoy a
        great time!</string>
    <!-- Resources for the Floris Bar (@www.florisbar.com/) -->
    <string name="floris_bar">Floris Bar</string>
    <string name="floris_bar_address">Impasse de la Fidélité 12, B-1000 Brussels</string>
    <string name="floris_bar_description">On the other side of the impasse from the Delirium Café
        you will find the Floris Bar. The Floris has its own specialty: you will travel back in time
        to an old Paris bistro to be introduced to a forgotten (in fact forbidden until recently)
        and resurrected drink: the famous Absinths (more than 400!) and very traditional ones: Gins,
        Whiskies (more than 200), anises and liquors.\n\nYou will be able to taste the Absinth in
        different ways: the traditional way with a lump of sugar and water dripping on it from a
        fountain, flamed in a shot or even in a pipe (and flamed as well!).\n\nHere as well, rarities
        and quality are priorities.\n\nPoets and artists welcome!\n\n« Hi, I\'m Charles, you must be
        Arthur? Or is it Paul? »</string>
    <!-- Resources for L'Atelier -->
    <string name="atelier">L\'Atelier</string>
    <string name="atelier_address">Rue Elise 77, B-1050 Brussels</string>
    <string name="atelier_description">L\'Atelier the place known by all the students, etc. a subdued
        atmosphere, wooden tables, a wide choice of beers, located right next to the university,
        this place still continues to please the less young.</string>
    <!-- Hotels Fragment Resource -->
    <!-- Resources for the Hotel Brussels Belgium (@www.hotelbrusselsbelgium.com) -->
    <string name="hotel_brussels_belgium">Hotel Brussels Belgium</string>
    <string name="hotel_brussels_belgium_address">Avenue Louise 315, B-1050 Brussels</string>
    <string name="hotel_brussels_belgium_description">With 70 square metre two-storey rooms, plenty
        of light streaming in through the large windows and Wi-Fi connection in all the rooms and the
        communal areas, the Brussels Hotel is the ideal backdrop for a business or family trip to the
        capital of Europe.\n\nThe Brussels Hotel is a modern, dynamic, relaxed hotel that is loved
        by families and businesspeople alike, located in the Louise district. Spaciousness
        characterises our hotel: the regular rooms measure more than 25 square metres, while the
        two-storey rooms, which can fit up to 4 people, measure 70 square metres.\n\nFor
        petit-dejeuner lovers, the Brussels is a great choice with its extensive buffet-style
        breakfasts. The hotel has an underground car park.\n\nThe Salon Louise, which is 60 square
        metres, is equipped with all the technology needed to hold company launches and other
        business events.</string>
    <!-- Resources for the Radisson Blu Royal Hotel Brussels (@www.radissonblu.com) -->
    <string name="radisson_blu_royal_hotel">Radisson Blu Royal Hotel Brussels</string>
    <string name="radisson_blu_royal_hotel_address">Rue du Fossé aux Loups 47, B-1000 Brussels</string>
    <string name="radisson_blu_royal_hotel_description">Featuring a modern Art Deco façade that
        includes a stunning atrium, glass dome and a river designed by renowned architect Michel
        Jaspers, the Radisson Blu Royal Hotel, Brussels is conveniently located in the city center.
        It offers easy access to the metro and major rail lines and Central Station is just 500
        meters away. Brussels Airport (BRU) is about 15 kilometers from the hotel and Brussels South
        Charleroi Airport (CRL) lies about 69 kilometers away. Popular attractions including the
        Grand Place, Manneken Pis and the BOZAR Museum are just a short walk from the hotel. Our 281
        rooms and suites features convenient amenities including satellite television as well as
        inviting décor in different signature styles: Urban Style, New York Mansion, Maritime and At
        Home. Guests can choose from 3 on-site restaurants: the Sea Grill restaurant, winner of 2
        Michelin stars, the unique PebbleWood Corner and the Atrium restaurant that features seasonal
        Belgian favorites. Guests can take advantage of underground parking and free access to the
        well-equipped Fitness Club which includes a 24-hour gym and a sauna. Business delegates can
        host meetings and conferences in one of our 18 meeting rooms that hold up to 420 guests.</string>
    <!-- Resources for the Hôtel Métropole (@http://www.metropolehotel.com) -->
    <string name="hotel_metropole">Hôtel Métropole</string>
    <string name="hotel_metropole_address">Place De Brouckère 31, B-1000 Brussels</string>
    <string name="hotel_metropole_description">A luxury hotel with an excellent reputation, the
        embodiment of Brussels\' most honored traditional values, spacious rooms and charming suites,
        with outstanding food.\n\nHotel Metropole, conveniently situated in the heart of Brussels,
        is famous for its warm welcome.\n\nOur guests will enjoy everything a city hotel has to
        offer. We invite you to discover the history of Brussels which comes to life in our hotel
        and to enjoy our high quality and comfortable hospitality.</string>
</resources>
